One day Tillu's family was travelling in a train.
Mom, I will sit near the window.
Yes yes son, sit down.  I am having a lot of fun.
Come and have your food.  You have not eaten anything since morning because of happiness.
Mummy, here too, Gal food.  Yes, what would you do?
Your miserly father doesn't get you anything on the train.
Yes, train food is the worst and most expensive.
Papa, which is our seat?
These two lower seats are ours.   Give a
tip.  First of all, we are three people.   If
Pillu had bought the team tickets, it would have cost more
and anyway you are still a child.
No dad, I want to sleep alone.  Now I am fine.   Okay
okay.  Don't shout, go to sleep
alone.